Bell Bottom - Twitter.com/TamilRasanai
reason behind this press-meet is
from 2,3 months
in our station limit
there has been 5-6 complaints regarding robbery in houses of people who live alone
behind this robbery
with the doubt that velayudham gang might have committed this
created team and started ground work
today morning at 6 am
the mall(loot) which this gang had been looted
with the information that they will be sold to merchant in koligudda
we caught them along with mall(loot)
mostly catching valuables costing eight lakhs is first in our district right ?
yes
well done sir,because of sincere officers like you,
faith among police forces has been increased among people
Thank You.. Thank You..
Subtitle Edited by TamilRasanai
Hemagiri inspector Parashuram bravery  !
-see man  ! -you are now hero sir  !
Higher officer is full happy now !
yesterday he called me and praised me so much !
we should try such brave things occasionally -yes sir  !
those prisoners should be handover to court at 11:30 AM
inform Hanumanthu and Rajashekar and do it
-what sir ? -where is the jewellery man  !
it was here only  !
-it was here only sir  ! -where it went then ?
(phone rings)
is there Detective Diwakar ?
what man Pandu ?
-Ramana catch ! -Mental  !
careful  !
don’t fall into prey by walking seeing sky !
get lost man  !
seems like yours has been excessively heat
-it might burn -who are you man  !
isn't boy's version itself has been changed ?
anybody there ?
remembers Pandus warning
Pandu  ! what an creepy mouth yours is  !
can anybody hear my voice ?
anybody at-least come and die....
hey you kid  !
even if you scream and break your veins, no one will come to help you
this is the yard where people wont come
who are you mother ? are you devil or satan that travels in this yard ?
need any special treatment ah ?
sorry grandma, now you only should save me like god
what will you give me if I save you ?
while i'm dying here ,this bloody grandma is speaking about deal
Ok tell me what you want ?
I have granddaughter who is of the age of marriage,you have to marry her
alas ! this grandma has planned of organising cock killing program by seeing innocent like me
I will inquire you after coming up -Ok done
first get me out of this
what if you cheat me after getting you out ?
human beings should believe one another grandma after all belief itself is life isn’t it ?
how can I give my granddaughter without knowing anything about you ?
so what ? should I read Purana with you ?
if you want to come up then you must read
what is your name ?
my name is Detective Diwakar
-your father ? -father Annappa
writer in Muddinakoppa station
mother Jalajakshi -she is no more
right from my childhood detective stories and movies were my favourite
are you reading ?
hey go father,i'm reading only
who killed Mahatma Gandhi ?
i'm asking you only who killed Gandhi ?
knife and fingerprints are found
only culprit has to be found
you bloody son  !
revenge of Deer elimination of enemy
while I told you to read are you wasting time by reading detective books ?
will wont ready daddy
will break your skull
will burn all -simply read
Announcement over Mic: All Come to See Dr.Raj upcoming movie Goa dalli cid 999
in Cinema: Tony.. Control yourself
you know that Tiger doesn’t likes if anyone tells a lie
take this
this is Transmitter watch
wear this whenever you meet him
record whatever he speaks there
-immediately you should go for Bangalore -Bangalore ah ha ha,I’m always ready sir
see guys
there are 3 huts in series side by side
among them,1st hut is been burning vigorously
now ambulance will come and for which hut it will pour water ? tell me
1st hut is been burnt, so obviously they should pour water for that
you fool,first hut has been burnt to ash
so in order to at-least save 2nd and 3rd hut,they will pour water for those two
am I correct Diwakara ?
hey Gurupada,why will ambulance come and pour water ?
isn’t that fire engines job ?
you crack good jokes man ! you confuse us with bare questions  !
that’s why you should listen properly when I ask
-eat carrot like me,even you people will become sharp -shall I go sir ?
why you behave like this father in law ? is this station to call as sir ?
where is your Defective Diwakara ?
see there he is sitting and doing meeting
oh what man Nimbehuli ?(nick name) how is the collection in station ?
if collection is more then ask him to get us Bonda(eatable)
he is greedy how will you expect him to bring Bonda ?
-see him father in law -hey he is fool,don’t care his words now you go
-Ok I will go -careful
your mother in law's son Suneela,has he became inspector ?
he is looking massive in inspector dress
why you people give build up for that ?
even Gurkha who guards city also wears khaki
-talk slowly man,your father also wearing khaki -hey get up man and go to home
Annappa will get angry,shall I go ? -goodnight
my elder sister's son Suneela
kid which grown up in front of my eyes
he has become inspector in our station
feels happy to see
even if buffalo pees,it looks like jogfalls for an ant's eye
for your capacity,try to become an inspector like him
or else,at-least try to become PC
PC ? ? (Laughing)
becoming PC and bucketing to senior officers,uff i cant even imagine such things
our aim is becoming a detective
sir  ! is there Defective Diwakar ?
you uneducated,its not defective its detective
im only Diwakar,tell me whats the matter ?
sir you are brilliant and intelligent in solving cases people are telling so
so we came near you to ask solution
this is our range
-how are saying so surely ? -i saw it from near man,its stomach was big
do you have more expirience than me ?
hey keep quiet man sir will decide whether it is pregnant or not..
-isnt it sir ? hey if he does pregnant how can i find man ?
tell me the matter properly
-in our house rat had been caught in rat trap
he says its pregnant that guy says it isnt you only should check and confirm it
(Father Laugh)
fools,should i even consider this as a case to solve ? came here for timepass ah ?
rat is the vehicle Lord Ganesh,if it is pregnant than it is like big sin for us
even if you are here for one more min i will kill you by feeding with rat poison
get lost
father Annappa
no need to troll that much even my time will come
even if kick your head against wall,i will wont become an inspector
-why you wont become ? -because i dont like it
-im your father telling you must wear -no means no. how much times should i say
why man why,why you wont become ?
according to law can anyone become detective just by reading detective books ?
dont underestimate me,i will prove myself by becoming detective
-you fool why cant you become an policeman ? -i wont and i will never
-you should become -i wont
-i will promise upon your mother you will become
is it ?
you were saying i will never ever become gurkha and now you become gurkha isnt it man ?
by becoming Police arent you standing like stone Diwakara ?
from now you are a cock which cant scream and bull which cant kick
assholes,trying to put kerosene into my wound get lost assholes
-hey L Board,come here man -came sir
hey go carefully
my name is Diwakara sir
wear that name in forehead and show to everyone
go to Bhaskar Shetty's hotel and bring everyone tea also bring this guy pulav
-me ?
-L board one kashaya -for me sugarless tea
-l board,for me badam milk -will throw on your head badam milk itseems
-sir for me one pack beedi -will put lathi inside your mouth
-traditional song chants
should kill everyone with rat poison
using me as servants to do their work
-L Board swami,buy my flowers please -get lost woman
-hey l board -sir
-clean this urine -me ?
what brings you laugh man
-Drama playing
what is this happened to your fate man ? it has became like dog touched pot
if i ever had to face this situation,i would rather die
sinking into this pot rather than facing this situation
M y life has became like broken shirt,
you people are laughing right ? are you people friends ?
drama continues
Diwakar:here im waiting to here an idea from you morons....
enough scolding us, there you see Romeo Annappa with Juliet Lalitha
if this romance continues,in near future you will have younger brother or sister to play
see man,do you want to play with born child
or will you stop their romance and save your house thats up to you
our Veera Abhimanyu went guys
-lalli -hmm
-let us go to Shirsi fest will you come ? -Annappa
-ok lets go -Annappa
-whats up ? have they put you in duty here ?
-story is good right -i didnt like
-why ?
whole city is witnessing your midnight romance,get up
hey,shut up man,dont speak nonsense
-appa,lets go to home -hey,leave my hands
-give that kadlepuri to her -hey leave my hands man
leave my hands man
you have no intention of my marriage,and you have started second innings
even im from department only take off your bloody hands you moron
dont fall into her trap by looking her white tone i had already warned
dont talk about her you fool its not good for us both
in the age of playing Chowkabaara are you trying to play Mallayuddha
Sahadeva
-what happened -big problem has been happened Sahadeva
the locked key is as it is without any change. key was with me only
there is no chance for any outsiders to come inside and steal the station
this job has been done by some insiders
first you enquire your staffs
i did that man,even they are innocents like me
even they are worried,dont know what to do
mall worth 8 lakhs if ever department comes to know about this then your job will gone
forget about job i will have to go for jail
what about my husband's case sir ?
we have given information to every station,you dont worry
lets search
what to do now man ?
sir take your ginger kashaya
-hey L board -sir !
this Madam has given complaint that her husband is missing
-this case you handle man -sir  ! me  !
why you give same expression for everything man ?
-hmm pick your gaandeeva use that Paspatastra gave by Lord Parameshwara
hey take her and start enquiring -thank you sir  ! !
come madam you are only my first case
-what to do now man ? -dont worry man
do one thing
give report to magistrate tomorrow itself
after mall identification parade we will be
having only 24 more days to submit mall to court
before that let us do something
-no the thing is... -now you go mann..
lets meet evening at bar
-ok
-what is your husband's name ? -its Anand
-age ? -45
-from when he is missing ? -how should i tell you sir..
-why ? -together we celebrated Sankranthi festival
but next day he said that he is going for job and till now he has not returned sir
-did he had illegal affair with anyone ? -sir  !
while having beautiful wife like me,why will maintain illegal affair ?
that is.. wont we put bedlamp in our house even
though Moonlight is so bigger and brighter ?
-even this is like that -my husband is not like that
he is like new avatar of Lord Shri Ramachandra  !
means even if he goes for forest or fasting those things will be done only with Seetha(you)  !
yes sir !
ok now you can go we will find your Rama ASAP
search him ASAP sir  !
thank god ! no one saw  !
Missing
come sir
see,this is the body
-what happened to you
-please dont cry
-you left me alone
-you go outside
oh goddess Laksmi bless me
from morning itself my fate itself is not good Khureshi
-where is your sir ? -he is inside seth ji,go
Ram Ram.. How are you sir ?
oh come Seth ji,come come
i have talked with revenue inspector,
you dont worry. keep your money ready
with your blessings,if that land becomes mine,
i will build cinema talkies and will put your big photo
what Seth ji,you are showing Dasara just with your words
your payment till now hasnt came
i came to give that payment only
please recieve
this is how real businessman's look like
-sir  ! -wait man
this month 20th, building will be auctioned
cant you see we both are talking ?
that is...Anuradha madam has arrived
see here
Seth ji  ! you can go now
if i require something i will inform you
who is this man ?
why are you standing ? please sit
my daughter is been crying daily by remembering him
-who should she call as father here after -im there na ?
means, i said that im there for your difficulties
it is very tough live as widow without husband in this society
please dont cry stay strong
if you cry then my eyes will be filled with tears
i think this is how fill in the blanks looks
-what are you starring at man ? -nothing sir
im learning how to consult women by looking at you sir
what happened to her husband's case ? did you get any evidence ?
sir what's the use of evidence if murderer himself has been found ?
murderer has been found ah ? who ?
dear Seethadevi can you please put forward your beautiful hand ?
-why ? -one minute
to put bangles into your hand
hey why are you putting this to madam's hand ? remove that L Board
one minute take this sir
her husband was killed by her sir not others
what nonsense are you speaking  ! why should i kill my own husband
-Mr.RaavanKumar -walk inside
got clarity ah ?
sorry sweetheart
sir..side please
this is the entamology report of her husband's body from forensic
if any person dies,after 7 days of decomposition germs called megats will formed in their body
depending upon the size of the megats germ
forensic team will find out how much days back person has been dead
according to this report, her husband has died 30 days back sir
but she gave complaint that 15 days back we both had
celebrated Sankranthi and after that he went missing
how did you celebrated festival with dead body ?
strange  !
when i started enquiry with this doubt,
we found out that she and her lover Ramesha had killed their husband
this is my enquiries report sir
even i would have became germ if i had lost my sense
first put them both inside locker
-put them Quereshi -come
-go man inside -i have not commited sir
i had underestimated you man
ever matter has reached even head office
you are worth for work
thats ok
where did you learnt about these germs ?
these are all basics sir they teach in training
is it ? i think i have bunked that class
-hey Shivarama.. -sir ?
-bring 2 cups tea for us -ok sir
more sugar please
if you find more such techniques
-tell me also -ha sir
-only when we are alone -ok sir
-hey come and take sweets man -whats so special bro ?
-hey quarter take sweeets -you look so happy
-whats so special ?
within 1 months of joining work,
my son has solved murder case with ease
entire station has been stunned  !
-take one more
-tiger itself grows inside tiger -then what ? isnt it ?
take... mysore pak
why one ? take entire box
everything is yours
celebration... mine or yours ?
yours only
then she is eating raw mango ?
dont give link for one another
she likes mango so she eats whats yours in middle ?
-i doubted that you made to sit Ganapathi(child) in gap -you put serial set then
i will bring puppet for kid to play
go man
if mother was alive,would she allowed you to do this ?
Annappa, come to home you have treat
-what ? even your station has been robbed ?
-yes man
Seth's shop jewellery had beeen robbed,
i had recovered that mall and kept in locker and i kept key with me
when i wake up at morning and saw locker is locked like before
but inside there is no mall(loot)
i cant even understand what's happening ?
Sahadeva
in the same style in front of press meet
both of them are robbed
-how is that possible ? -even i cant understand that
even pressmeet knows everything about mall which we have recovered
after calling jewellery owners
we have to do mall identification and should submit to court
what shall i do now ?
if SP comes to know about this we will loose job
also have to go for jail
to solve this case,
a very good officer required
means,
can we officially handle this case ?
submitting this case to private detective is better according to my opinion
what you are telling is ok man,
if he has robbed our station itself
imagine how genius he would be  !
to catch such guy,even our detective should be genius
along with that he should be trustworthy too
for that
in my station there is one genuis
hot ghee
if you swallow then throat will burn
if you throw then you will be caught
overall difficult to breath situation
now you only have to do something Diwakara
we shall do something dont worry
i will myself solve this case
but, i have my own conditions
what are those ?
first one-from tommorow onwards i will come to station whenever i wish
no one should ask why and what
ok
along with that i require a jawa bike
my conditions are not finished
one more major condition is remaining
whats that ?
anyhow im in professional field
you should make some report
showing my unefficiency or may be women harrasment or rude behaviour
and somehow you should write false negative reports
should provide a report to department
and should remove myself from this job
are you even mad ?
everyone die for promotion and increment
while you are telling to remove you from job
by writing negative report
what else should i do swami ?
dreamt of swimming in ocean
but my father Annappa,
pushed me into the well which has no water
if my conditions are ok for you, then your deal is ok for me
alright your fate
got freedom from lifetime imprisonment
shall i go ?
this is the heartwrenching story of Diwakar grandma
you are roaming without job like useless moron
what is the use of saving a guy like you ?
die there itself
grandma
instead of saving,you are telling me to die and moving  !
granny crow
after hearing story went like crow
let your mouth swollen let your tongue teared
let face rotten you fall sick
grandmaa..
-who is that -you scold nicely
hey girl who are you ?
where is that granny crow ?
girl is also me grand maa is also me
that means this much time you fooled me that you were grandmaa
hear carefully
you cant even find out who is girl who is women when i change my voice
-and you also a detective(teases)
-dont make me angry
whoever you might be first get me out
i can't
hey why you can't ?
why cant i will ask
because even i have fallen into a hole
which nearer to hole which you have fallen
even im tired of screaming for asking help like you
sat silently without getting any idea to come up same like you
after hearing your screaming for help
i thought of making timepass so simply acted like helping you
while im almost dying here for you timepass ah ?
no need James Bond.. here there are heavier stones
your head will be squashed watermelon if i throw them carefull
see, both are in same situation
instead of fighting think a way to come up
how can i find a way ? this is minimum 15 feet
not even a single creeper or rope is there to try and climb up
if there is no creep plant whats the problem
isnt there any things which are like rope ?
there is nothing like that here
you are Detective right ? think then
in tough times boys mind wont work maa
you only tell what's that plan ?
remove you pant,shirt,baniyan and...
and....
tie one another and throw into this hole with all your power
after throwing... ?
should i stand naked ?
let me finish first
from this side even i will remove my all clothes and..
and..
first control your that feeling
why should i have that feeling. ?
after tying my dress to your dress, i will throw one end of the dress into your hole
catch that strongly
come up with its support after that i will pick you up
-is that ok -extraordinary plan..  !
but small change in plan that is..
first i will come outside then i will get you out
-ha come then -yeah sure will come
are you thinking of enjoying with lone girl ha ?
im fan of Disco Shanthi
we have huge respect upon women
already you have trapped me
what if you cheat me again.. ? so i asked so...
oh is that your problem ?
ok first you only climb up
remove your clothes now
just a min will remove it....
Singing happily
i finished removing.. did you ?
-wait im removing... -remove
take this
take this catch
have you holded tightly ?
-ha,you climb once -ha i understood
im coming hold it
-you.. ? -yeah me only man
-Kusuma -you told that you had fallen in hole ?
but i cant see any holes here ?
simply i lied..
didnt you remove your clothes then.. ?
why dear.. ? are you thinking that things which you had dreamt went wrong ah ?
if i see grown up man half naked, then its very good for me written in todays horoscope
so i played a small game
playing games with me ha ?
if i dont remove your saitan using itching leaves then my you can change my name
wait
see here
is that Lion or Tiger to get feared
after all its an lamb
what you think you are wearing Karna's shield ah ? after all leaves and bush
Raja.. came at righ time come
who is he sister ?
Digambara (naked saint of Jain)
Diwakara not Digambara...
my lamb will decide whether you are Diwakara or Digambara
shall i leave it ?
shall i leave.. ?
-shall i ? -hey no.. !
play one song
just with words i had almost lost my ...self respect
-Carrot juice,palav,side dish,laddoo,vada -eat
whats this dad ? entire cooking is full of carrot
you are now handling big case, so you need to have good intelligence
-if he eats this much carrot, wont his intelligence leak out.. ?
-hey fool sit quietly
you dont know to prepare these items right. ?
-see here
forgot to give Carrot halva.. take this
give
are you both planning to make me eat halva ?
nowadays yours has become over..
first this window should be removed and wall has to be built
he is handling bigger case than me
Hey Kureshi.. that Diwakar is crazy guy keep an eye on him until this case finishes
why just keeping eyes sir ? i will be with him only
oh L Board sir  ! in civil dress
looking like Chandrashekar of Edakalagudde
are you actress Aaarathi or Jayanthi ?
your reckless behaviour has become more control that
what man L Board ? you are looking Tiptop
Constable Kureshi reporting sir..
hey Mahadeva, go and bring strong tea for sir
sir ah  ! ?
from now onwards he is not PC he is Detective Diwakar
everyone should give respect understood.. ?
Sugar Extra.. go
by the by Kureshi, can i get a Chalk Piece ? 1 min let me check sir..
traditional song chant
-oh L Board sir  ! -how did you know that its me  ! !
for normal people there will be two eyes
for blind people entire body itself is like eyes
only you eat carrot in this station sir  !
Genius..
this is overall map of our Jenukallu Taluk
Correct ah ? Correct sir..
so, will start enquiry from this Hemagiri station
-dear Siddharaju.. -sir
in which prison those prisoners who have robbed kept ?
-Amruthooru jail sir
Hi.. sir how are you ? Fine..
-i required some case files -sure sir ! why not ? pls come..
no Quereshi, this is not the work of normal regular robbers
someone who thinks creatively has done this
someone like that means...
ha sir there is one guy  !
-who  ! -Goobe Rama (owl Rama)
Goobe Rama ah ? name itself is strange man  !
not only name, even that guy is also strange sir  !
-what do you want ?
next saturday is my grandfather's thithi (funeral function)
to eat holy rice bar's what we keep for crows, i required three crows sir
there is our boy
give him your list
give information of how much you need, which place ?
and pay advance with him now and you can go
-ok sir i will go -ok ok
-baiyya -no swamy thing is...
-police has arrived -police  !
-you please stand aside -ok swamy
owl seva,crow seva lizard seva,pig seva,parrot seva
what are these man ?
this is the list of all sevas that you get here sir  !
get lost dog  !
what is this owl seva ?
when people who live in rented house wont pay rent to owners,
thats when owners come and do this seva with us
we will place owls inside their house without their knowledge
they leave house thinking that it's bad sign
that's it
and you named this bullshit job as seva ah ?
what are parrot,rat and lizard sevas then ?
these are all side business profit is less in those
those who see horoscopy
like parrot,mouse and so on we give these by mastering them
they earn their daily bread because of us
and here you see this lizard seva  !
no matter how many times you need for hearing good sign or bad sign
just give me a signal at that time lizard will make sound
how you master those small lizards mann  !
what are you saying sir  !
the only thing which cannot be mastered in this world is our tongue
other than that we can master every animal
kureshi
this guy will even sell comb for a bald guy
this guy only robbed police station arrest him  !
what are you saying sir ?
me robbery  ! that too in police station ?
i have left thefting a long back sir..
while having this kind of faboulous job here,
why should i durt my hands by robbing again
you might have not done but you could have used others to do what will you say ?
what plan can i give sir ?
im not such bad guy as you think
i remembered one thing when you said about plan
one guy was in jail for seven years now from two years he is outside
at present he is working in timber shop at Keradi
big khatarnak now he cant steal
he is aged, still gives best ideas for those who steal
-whats his name ? - his name is MaraKutuka(wood pecker)
-did you find myself ? -why ?
im in changed identity sir
your head..changed identity itseems where is he ?
come
-who are you ? whom you want ? -i wanted to see your dad Marakutuka
he is not my dad he is the one whom i have married
hey fool, somebody has came for seeing you
young lemon fruit for that old tamarind tree ah  !
what if tree is old, tamarind isnt old she is his fifth wife
-fifth wife ah  ! -yes
his name itself is Marakutuka so wood pecking itself is his job
-alas Marakutuka  !
-take -she is 4th wife,3rd one ran away
she is second wife sir
we needed a plan to steal
-place hundred rupees
-what is he telling ? -wait sir
-give me here -heyy
tell me
which is the place ?
is it Bank,House or Temple ?
Pushpagiri police station
-leave me,i have to drop children to school -come here
she is first wife sir original
are we here for population sensus ?
dad i need 2 rupees
-why ? -to watch movie
will kick with my sandals if you come again for money
(whispering)
why should i steal police station after all ?
our Mall has been stuck in station
eight male constables
3 female constables
one among her is beautiful
one flat nosed ASI one half cracked SI
you are telling that you will steal from a
place where entire city goons,thiefs are kept
-hi chan,chu,chup... hey what is that word -impossible
no chance !
dont go, dont do leave this plan
you will be finished
-i will look after whatever happens
you give me the plan
we will support if someone wants to plough land using cart of cow
we wont support if you want to hang yourself using that cart
then pay back money which we gave
until we beat it will be log once we beat it will be wood
once you give its gone now get up
get up guys
ok, has anyone came near you before us with station robbing plan ?
why you want that ?
if you dont say we know how to make you tell truth
hey what will yo.....
brother
is everyone fine ?
you asked to make bed, its almost ready
sir, newly appointed Detective sir
-who kept alchohol here -let it be man, keep there
i made mistake sir,leave me sir sorry sir
come here sir
sir here sir please sir
i dont have any money sir
-everything is yours sir -come here
they are wives,many childrens, i have left that field sir
is there anyone who robs police station in this taluk ?
one guy is there sir
-who is that ?
its dried
Pete...
-sagani(gobar)... sagani pinto -sagani pinto ah  !
you dont know that sir !
time has been worst now
-even for good guy like me only... -namaskar bro
what ?
4 pack Pinto brand vibhoothi(holy ash) 1/4 kg bronze plate after that..
give that bhusambra and 2 dozen bronze pot
50 grams Ranjika, 10 meter fat chain
2 packets camphor
take this and tell to your boss that i gave you
ok bro
-how do you know him ?
what are you asking sir ! he is very intelligent maniac
from many years he hasnt slept properly sir
why ?
he is suffering from sleeping disorder Insomania
lives alone. doesnt have wife, children and all
he is not the type of thief whom rob for money
he steals for thrill such a starnge character  !
many times,
after returning stolen mall
tells to be carefull for mall owner  !
according to law,
we dont have single proper evidence to put him inside locker
he has perfectly swallowed and knows our law
Tsunamic moron
where can i get him ?
there is Kumbarapete Meenakshi theatre right ?
he does camphor,agarbatthi and stays on back of that
like Marakutuka told, he might have done this
why Sagani(gobar) along with Pinto ?
will you excrete gobar ?
Song: if you place then i will be gobar
if you roll that then i will be compost
if you burn, then i will be Vibhoothi(holy ash)
i collect gobar from surrounding people and i prepare Vibhoothi
so people call me with love Sagani Pinto
two Pintos and two sagani ha ?
no sir, one sagani and one Pinto
where were you when January 12 night ?
sir it was full moon day
there was Durgamma temple fest.. Even i had kept an stall  !
if you tell lie, then we should start police treatment
lie  !
i have believed truth as my home god.
will i tell lie sir ?
sir that day many devotees had came for temple
even i did 500 rupees business on that day !
sir, why asking that with more stress ?
-there has been robbery at one place
-robbery ah  !
without closing milk vessel properly we shoudnt call cat as thief
we should be carefull ourselves
what is this sir ?
your dress has been dirted badly
see there that ant is eating sugar
just because its eating sugar, can we call it as thief ?
we cant sir because thats nature
quereshi sir whats this ?
you have kept station so untidy ?
for us station is like temple
even should feel happy to come to this holyshrine
every now and then isnt it ?
i just said thats it
-ok now you go
-why so hurry ?
-we will call you if we need anything ok sir
i will go sir
Quereshi, this Pinto is chess player i agree but i dont
feel that he has enough courage to play with station
dont come to conclusion so fast
everytime suspect will be much more brilliant than us
observe his activities carefully dont leave him
in poster: Hasida Hannu movie playing
there wil be evidences in things which he finished using
once check those
-you should go only after watching entire cinema -ok sir
-tell me story afterwards ok ? -ok
who will watch this cinema once if he finishes battery
bloody experience those morons have
-why late ? -nothing, come inside come
-why these guys are screaming ?
-dont know sir
sir im already late, i will go
-sister ?
-finished business ?
everything is finished,will go another round
ok
-sis, i'm going back
-also ask remaining debt from Shetty -18 rupees,
i will bring that
-Detective Digambar, come -mind your words
-Diwakar not Digambar..
what are you doing here ?
-all these are looking quiet suspicious
no need to suspect these are illegal black alcohol only
i will seize them by putting case
daily your inspector will be provided with 2 bottles from here itself
come and sit
that bloody asshole wont even leave anything
-degrading our department dignity
-did you find theives ?
will be caught were will they go without getting ?
-will put everyone in locker
-do you have such brain to catch thieves ?
intelligence is our bloodgroup
then shall we play a game ?
if you win in that then i myself will agree that you are brilliant
if you lose than you should agree that you are waste
-is it ok
-floodlight match
whats that Kabaddi,Kockoo or hide and seek game ?
there is basket behind you.. Take that
took
sit looking that side
done with that
now take kavade(astrology stones) of any number not more than ten
took
now take same number of stones in the name of king
this guy also... done
now i will give you six stones
keep them also
-done -now calculate total stones
give half of them to god
-done -now pay back what you took from king
done with that his debt it seems
now shall i say how much do you have remaining ?
-tell me -three
-how did you find out perfectly  !
-you are brilliant right then find out
shall i go ?
how is this possible ? did she saw ?
-step aside
-ah ?
has she learnt Kavadeshastra or what ?
hey Defective Digambar did you find out how it is ?
L board sir, why are you looking strange sir !
hey Jayanthi get lost
father in law !
what raja did you find out that maths ?
Always you will be in your own world  !
Go and see your work
if one could become brilliant just by eating
carrot, then our goat would have been scientist now
want carrot ?
-ivy guard ? -no need
she gave six
remaining three
six.. half of six is three
here is our shining Chintamani
bro give me some water to drink
take this
by thinking about fish, im now in restlessness situation
-so i came
-same for me also
i came running with fear that fish will die cause of evaporation of water
-Kusuma !
-dont you think we both think in same way !
isnt it !
fish is like life for me and even for you  !
if so, then why not we both should love each other ?
means... you have fallen in love with me !
i will promise upon this fish
-confirm right !
-100%  !
why late then ? if we go to register office just fifty rupees fees
then bring two garlands, and one guy as proof from both sides
entire marriage will be finished in just half an hour !
i will do all essential things that has to be done in newly married couples house
also..let our first night also be finished tonight itself..
i didnt even finished 1 min conveying my love but you have started even family !
we should understand each other, we should share our feelings
do you think marriage is like kids play ?
then what you think loving is kid's play ?
how did you love without thinking anything ?
are you thinking of playing since girl is beautiful ?
there is huge difference in taste between those mangoes grown in trees and
to those which are hybrid grown by injecting chemicals
same way even this love is
tip should grow into flower flower should grow into seed
then seed should grow into fruit
understood ?
1 minute
stand there !
i grown in mango farm
even i know i seed changes into fruit
you had given a sum right ?
i have solved
if you give six then three remains at the end
if its four then remains two half of the given sttones will be remained at end
this is the trick right ?
you have become brilliant after joining me
dont shake much you will be in first step if you fall
look after fish carefully
i didnt see anything
kusuma i love you
Karnataka state lottery luck goddess is coming to your door step
who gets and why not !
-who is this monkey race sir ?
-bless god
what are you doing here ?
i wanted to tell you something so i came looking you
-whats that ?
-that is..
if you want to understand wolf then be a goat
if you want to understand a girl then become a play boy
our Beechi (famous poet) used to say
Stop that and tell me what you wanted to say
ok then.. i think you are not handling case properly
because,
my opinion is we have to think like thief to catch a thief
you gobar
if i kick you i should clean my leg
and you are advising me to catch thief
there is an quote that no one is younger than me
no is elder than Shivasharanas
im not eligible to advise you
thought of telling you so i said
rest is upto you
i will go
forgot to say
take this
should submit
should present yourselves
when did you stole these all things  !
see that ant it is eating sugar
how untidy you have kept the station Quereshi sir ?
why shirt is so dirty ?
without closing milk vessel properly we shoudnt decide cat as thief
not every thief will be as good as me
now onwards be carefull !
if we are careless, then this guy might even remove our Kidney and sale
you will be along with me in this case
its like even essence of flower reaching heaven along with flower
ok sir
-then me sir ?
-if he is essence then you are root
-is anything playing ? -no man nothing
shake it properly Pandu
im shaking only see properly man
it hasnt came shake properly Pandu..
-see properly Diwakara
-no
-coughs -i think now its playing
isnt he there ?
-why ? -coffee
he doesnt drink hot coffee give him when it gets enough colder
is this much enough ?
In News: Today morning after thefting state bank in Muthuraj circle,
the theives have been caught by Suneela and team of
Mudinakoppa police station by chasing who were trying to escape
valuables of cost six lakh has been siezed
Police Department has praised the braveries of Suneela and his team
-is there inspector ?
-he is there sir
-Suneela...
-whats the matter Diwakara ?
you have come running these long ?
-to see father-in law ah ?
-no
saw today's news
-is 6 lakhs seized after arresting bank robbers ?
-yes
-where have you kept mall ?
-its in locker
open it
why man ?
-you open, i will say
-why what happened ?
-why are you so tensed ?
-you open it first
whats the matter ?
thank god !
nothing has happened
-what should have happened ?
-you lock first
come
-is it ?
-hmm
till the day of submission to the court i will guard it day and night
-no need of any risk
-dont worry, even i will be there
im staying here today because of one investigation
tomorrow morning until i say,
no one should come inside this room
whatever case comes, you should attend it outside
and should send them
everyone's cooperation is important everyone should stay alert
-this is my sincere request
-ok sir
even i will see how they will rob
-who is that -tea sir
-can't you see him coming ? -sorry sir
-keep that tea there and go
-ok sir
i doubt what work these guys are doing
our cow has been lost we want to give complaint with sir
sir is busy come tomorow morning
-i just want to speak with sir
-not possible now, see you tommorow
-Mr.Srinivas, -sir ?
give them two rupees there itself and send them
-dont let them inside
-ok sir
-hey stop there. where are you going ?
-wanted to see Diwakar
he is busy meet him tomorow morning
we both are his close friends
we even bought tickets for second show let us go inside
sir has told not to allow anyone get lost
whats this bro ?
-whats the matter guys ?
-wanted to see sir
now can't come tomorrow morning
dog has bitten his son-in law and dog has died
have to check whether it is pregnant or not ?
are you guys doing comedy here ?
if you know whom we are then you will be finished
will you go or should i beat you hard ?
hey stop there
whats the matter ?
sir asked to bring honey so i wanted to give
give here i will only give
pot honey so should be given only to sir
he is busy meet him on morning
what are you starring at ? get lost
enough laughing now you can go
even paper has came and also my show finished
Diwakara.. those inspectors are not at all trustworthy
they might have acted to loot money
how can they come inside when many staffs are very much alert ?
see here, how strong the locker given by government is
can they loot by breaking this locker ?
whats happening here Diwakara ?
what ?
finally they broke our own station
hey Diwakara.. you are of no use man
you are biggest fool
police people shoudnt believe their own hands
whether he might father or son, you should doubt him
what if the inspectors whom gave you this job has done this ?
dad, first of all my head is full of shit now you dont give more headache
no Diwakara this is definitely not done by humans
something unusual is happening under our eye sight
to solve this Moady Nanjappa himself is best
Moady Nanjappa ah ?
who is that ?
he knows every black magics
draw the Mandala there
chants manthra
hundred percent sure that this is not the problem caused by saitans
there is the hand of some people
there is also some wonder which you cannot
see through your naked eyes
listen brother
you went too much closer to it and came back
those have escaped from you from a seconds gap
dont leave them use your brain for this
use this oppurtunity wisely
surely they will be caught
Nanga Devi is giving indications
hear this with utmost concentration
this life is like a seesaw
girl with attractive pettycoat
eyes which never ever gets dreams
black magician with chants power
minister above him
hope everything goes fine
is this guy a miracle man for you ?
shut up, dont talk like that
there will be secret meaning behind his words
your head
if you are into department with influence
than this happens. see there
dont neglect bro
have some fear or else you will experience
now what ?
your conclusion should be cleared isnt it ?
do one thing, im only thief so arrest me and put inside jail
dont speak like fool
you are not understanding my pressure
why you loved me if you had that much pressure ?
i had already told you
should i think about love for entire day ?
think man who said not to think ?
but dont sit tentioned like this
no matter how much rod has been heaten,
hammer should be cool to do work
understood ?
remove your cap
remove that
if buffalo has bathing problem then
ox has kicking problem
if i ask you to find robbers you are
spending your time chatting with girl
-not like that sir
-dont open your mouth,shut up
when did i gave you this case ?
you were not able to collect single evidence in all these days
even though cant do anything,
still posing with getup like this
-im enquiring sir
-what the hell are you enquiring ?
i should submit this mall to court within one week
you will survived if you find out theives within that gap
otherwise.. i will make your life a hell..
you dont know about my influence
you shoudnt be promoted nor be removed
i will make you die in the centre lifelong
why is your face is so dull ? laugh sis
move your head slightly
this side...
-sir when will you give me photos ?
-tomorrow night come fast, i will give you
why are you sitting like this ? what happened to you ?
that inspector Sahadeva insulted me in front of everyone
my prestige went in vain i should do something to him
you concentrate upon case i will play football with that Sahadeva
i have some work will meet later
who is this asshole disturbing me when im in mood ?
boss !
whats the matter boss ?
its like Lord Krishna coming to his devotees house
-havent brought food for lord is it ok ?
-big words sir !
Pinto.. come
lets go sir
-Pinto ?
-boss ?
i had guarded it without closing my eyes
in front of me itself money went missing
-is that happened ? -yes man !
these black magics.. are they really there in reality ?
what are you speaking boss ?
i remember Kuvempu's poem when i heard your words
day to day game is found between sunrise and sunset
your head will be there
instead of giving build up like this tell me properly
-how to tell this man ?
-tell somehow
now..
see that thing there
whats so special in that ? see this calender now
one..two..three
fire  !
what are you seeing there sir ? see that pot
whats there in that ?
dont feel excited for just these things see in it
whats this my face has been powdered ?
are you a magic ?
or is magic inside you ?
sir the things you seen now its pure magic !
but there is a logic behind that
in this world even a small worm doesnt move without a logic
i will call this as perfect science !
you showed entire world within two minutes !
big words sir !
sir dont forget ! you are Diwakara ! Detective Diwakara  !
that thief cant escape by fooling your eyes ! forget that,
im 100% sure sir ! you will catch him sir !
you are the only one who spoke about me positively
you said i love you right !
do you know what poet Bendre said about....
its ok
my dear Saroja !
as how bee is attracted towards flower,
as how see is attracted towards waves,
i have completely lost and attracted towards your beauty Saroja !
today evening near Chakori tree,
i will be waiting for you
yours lovely tiger-Sahadeva
hey Saroja, where have you kept my lathi ?
it might be there itself see properly
im asking you only come and search
what kind of house is this ? things disappear from the place where it is kept
its here only cant you see properly ? take
if wife shows her dull face like this, no work will be done properly
Sahadeva, you are Mahadeva of mine
come and lower my pain of broken heart
satisfy the urge of this young age
this soul is waiting for you only
i will be waiting for you at evening near Chakori tree
yours lovely Saroja !
considering my vast experience,
90% cases are solved through pyschological test
what is that thing ?
one minute, i will show you one thing
hey Nanjunda come here
-what sir ? -whats your plans man ?
why sir ? is playing football some offense ?
playing football is not a problem playing with balls is problem
what ? heard that you are preparing ragi flour vigourosly ?
do you think that we wont know about your things ?
its good for you if you tell me otherwise
i will spread your love matter to entire city
i havent done anything wrong
when i came to Putmalli ragi mill to fill flour, current gone sir
things went wrong in that dark night sir
please dont tell her father sir
i havent done anything wrong she falled upon me
see sir
simply throwed a stone see how fruit has fallen !
he naked himself !
why did you accepted things just for his words !
who am i(singing)
whats the matter ?
let us try this pyschological test upon him and shall find truth
come here
just a min bro
want some tea ?
do you think nobody here knows about your matter ?
we know what things you do inch by inch
we took photos of everything
since how many days this has been going on ?
what work bro ?
its better to you to accept the truth, or else i will spin your both hands
catch him
stop there
-catch him -catch
-pick him up -get up
why you ran ?
i have promised my sister that i will wont tell to anyone
i havent done anything wrong im doing as per my sisters instructions
i beg you please leave me
already im in tension say properly
where have you kept mall ?
thats behind sisters home
you bastard !
im searching entire village for thief
how did you robbed station in front of my eyes !
theft  ! what are you talking brother ?
i told about blackmall(alchohol)
blackmall ah ?
sister !
-what happened Raja ?
-see them
they are beating me telling that i stolen their station
if you cant catch theif,
will you show your arrogance towards innocent ?
-no Kusuma
-shame on you
dont show your disgraced face to me here after..
Come Raja..
it was the best case which i had caught
dreamt of becoming circle inspector by getting promoted
but now my future itself is in threat
if i wont get mall, then confirm i will be in jail
nothing will happen like that
i will solve this case
what will you solve ?
till now you are not able to collect even a single evidence
whats this man ? Kavade(stone) ? soaked with kunkum
whats this ? wont you sweep daily ?
Sarojamma is in leave since for her daughters marriage
so we are only sweeping on alternative days
you are cheating
come this side !
now you beat !
Siddharaju !
take out complaint history
who all had came to station during the night of robbery ?
see
brothers had came from Iduvani because of land issue
-to give complaint
-next
rowdy sheeter Narasimha had came from neighbour village
other than that ?
blind people had came begging
-blind people had came right ?
-yes sir
blind people had came begging also to our station during that robbed night
give them 2 rupees there itself and send them
first of all they have no house man !
their presence at spot during robbery might be coincidence !
im not feeling like that Gurupada
there is somethink linked to them and station robbery
tomorrow whole day,
let us keep an eye upon their activities
what did you find out ?
im not getting clarity !
they are feeding themselves by singing and begging
what more clarity do you need ?
wait ! heard some sound there
-lets go man
-wait !
whats this ?
whats this ? what are you doing ? who is he ?
sorry sir we thought rat and mongoose is fighting in bush
madam arent you Hucchukudure movie heroine Hema  !
Autograph Please madam..
get lost from here.. if you do over,
will put inside
sir will put inside it seems, let us go
there will be thorns in bush carefull !
will thorn harm another thorn ?
tell madam to be carefull !
carefull madam !
hey Gurupala lets go
i will come man wait
hey Kureshi..
how if we catch these blind people and work ?
its sensitive matter sir
if we touch them without evidence then we will be in trouble
whats big matter if they came to station ?
they used to come to our station also
they dont have any time speculations
they will come morning sometimes even night
i have enquired those who came when station was robbed at night
but thieves might have collected information at morning.
what you think ?
yes sir ! i didnt think in that angle !
why should you think ? its my job right ?
anyway thank you..
i will go
afterwards i will see you..
there will be lawyers, thieves and so on will be coming
since its police station
such suspiscious persons havent came sir
during pressmeet time,
one girl had come to give complaint that her tenth marks card has been missing
same complaint has been registered even in our station also on that robbed day !
girl named Mary Thomas has given complaint
even in our station in girl gave complaint regarding same issue
but her name is Geetha not Mary Thomas
-is there complaint copy ? -it is there
see this sir
take it sir
all three has same handwriting
means..,
Same girl has given complaint in different names
how was she looking like ?
do you remember anything regarding
her activities in station that day ?
no sir i cant remember
forgotten her face
i dont remember
but, she had came during pressmeet time
i had asked her to wait 10 min and made her sit outside
do you have any photos of that day ?
we dont have sir but if we ask with press people they might have it
usually we wont develop every photos
i feel there is a girl in this pic
see it might help you
-check is it her ? -yes sir the same girl !
its her
no doubt ! this is Kusumas hand writing
this is her
Pallavi Bar
i cant understand whom to believe and whom not
are you sure she gave police complaint ?
hundred percent sure
but i cant understand one thing
the day robbery happened, she also visited station
even blind people came to station
im the thief arrest me and put in jail
you scared me man !
-give me kercheif
-take
give me that
post has arrived
why are you pouring everything to me ? you have some
its ok drink you should be happy
enough now itself i have taken more
why are you forcing him eventhough he says enough ?
before sacrifying Goat,
we will place a garland around its head this is also same
by fooling me as friend you are romancing with
my own wife what kind of bastard you are !
someone has lied you to spoil our friendship
do you think i will do such things ?
see what will you say for this ?
you are the street dog whom raise the leg for all trees
by fitting case upon both of us and by sending us to jail
you have planned of enjoying with my wife
-put that down
-leave that
-leave my hand
-i will kill you
-Sahadeva leave that gun
-i will wont spare you
this is more than enough to play with them
you are looking beautifull in this dress
you didnt even imagine that i will be here right ?
why you are here ?
i came to give food
where are they ?
why that much concern towards them ?
even i have same concern towards you
i wanted to enquire you
so i came to take you dragging
please will you come ?
i thought you were Sadhvi B Saroja Devi
but you are dacoit Poolan Devi
-i know everything
-what you know ?
Yashoda
Geetha
Mary Thomas
what are these ?
i think now you will get clarity
this handwriting is yours only
so what should i do ?
station was robbed by none other than you !
since you didnt get culprits,
are you trying to frame me into this ?
the day robbery happened,
you have given complaint to 3 stations in different names
why ?
just because i have went to watch Dasara, you are
blaming me for stealing Ambari (God's monument)
what proof do you have to prive me as thief ?
even blind people have went for all 3 stations the same day
what is the link between me and that ?
without any link or relation you came there to give them food ah ?
is giving food for needy is crime ?
same like me, many bring in this city bring food for them
law requires proof
not your cooked up stories
if you have guts,
prove me as thief
i will myself surrender in station
instead of that
if you try to swim without knowing it,
you will be drown
carefull !
according to law,
what she said is right
no case stands without evidence
for law, proof is more important than truth
what you were saying was right dad
we cant become detectives just by reading books and cinemas
even though accused was in front of me i was helpless
i cant do this dad
why you feel sad for that ?
these are all common in our job
only after burning, pot becomes stronger
in my life, i never smoked a full cigerate
even after that, how my hands burnt that day ?
that also both me and Suneela
means,
did we lost our sense for 8 minutes that day ?
physically no one injected us drugs
still we lost our sense
is there a chance of injection of drug or any other chemical in any other way ?
what did i eat that day ?
what did i drink ?
will it be in powder form ?
whats this man ? my face has been powdered ?
after all by sparkling powder,
you made me loose my sense !
for the shock treatment we give to him,
he should permenantly sleep in coma
why are showing this much anger towards me Boss ?
every happiness is a missed tragedy
in the same way,
every tragedy is missed happiness
isnt it ?
robbed station and telling lies with me
i havent theft station boss
somebody has given you the wrong information
dosage is enough ? or you want more ?
enough... enough boss
i will tell everything
what happened means.....
-come this side
-just once more..
i told you to come na ?
Boss.. tell him,
he is giving current alternatively can this body tolerate ?
tell.. why did you robbed station ?
i will tell the truth boss,
i didnt do station robbery
do you know what happened boss ?
you sing well..
oh L Board sir ! what makes you come here ?
wanted to organise music concert of you
music concert ah ? where sir ?
in central jail
now you go.. go
by applying leave for duty, did you brought her to mountain ?
while im struggling here with case and all,
are you playing hide and seek with your Kidney ?
hey shut up dont speak nonsense
give it here
what makes you bring sweets ?
did you get any evidence ?
why evidence ? i have caught even culprits !
what  !
i cant believe that blind people have involved in it  !
thats the tricky point in this case dad
no one will believe that they have robbed
in fact that case doesnt withstands in any courts
by taking this as advantage,
those have made this job by using them (blind people)
how is this possible after all ?
first,the information of mall in station was collected,
Kusuma used to go there with the intention of giving complaint
sir marks card was lost,
i have to give complaint
how many staffs are there,
what is there in which place,
recovered mall is kept in which locker,
like that she used to observe every things and matter
after that she returned to home,
upon a dress which has square shaped designs,
she used to stich Kavades(stones),
and prepared a map of station
after that,
she used to train us for robbery using map contained kerchief
means by making us to sleep
they used to rob in front of police itself ah ?
yes sir
she is very brilliant girl !
by the way..
just by this agarbatthi smell they used to sleep ah ? how is that ?
they were loosing their sense not through agarbatti smell dad,
but because of a drug called "Devils Breath"
Devils Breath ah ?
there is a plant called Datura in Columbia nation
with the seed which came from fruit of this plant,
they extract a drug called "Devils Breath"
if we sprinkle this drug into any person
or even if someone breathes it
he will be stunned for eight minutes
he cant notice anything that happens around during that time
this Devils Breath drug was supplied to all of them,
in the form of powder through Sagani Pinto
alas this asshole  !
how did Pinto get this drug ?
it was supplied illegaly
for all black magicians, i used to supply
means did you get the lost mall ?
no dad
these Pinto gang had only postman job
there is a man behind all of them
is it ?
who is he ?
he is much closer to you
you also have meeted him once i say !
-Gurupada do it
-no no no
i will say
black magician Nanjappa
hey you brother !
why you hurt yourselves by hitting me ?
even if you kill me i wont reveal the secret !
i have given words to my Boss
my secret will be burried along with me
this is were i have stuck dad
oh my god ! what kind of network they have ?
only doubt is who is the Boss behind Moadi Nanjappa
that is...robbery happened in police station
whatever plan Kusuma does,
my doubt is that there might be an Mastermind who knows
geography, biography of the station behind this plan
who is such mastermind in our area ?
ha i understood !
-who ?
-Marakutuka  !
correct dad ! he didnt flashed to me  !
he was the only guy i had left
definitely ! he is the Boss of them
such small thing didnt flashed to me dad !
every culprit is in my surroundings itself
this is like,
asking address with police after stealing a car
what kind of police im  !
now every dot is connecting
girl with beautiful pettycoat-Kusuma
eyes which never gets dream-Pinto
black magician with mantras power-Moadi Nanjappa !
minister above him-Annappa !
-which Annappa man ! -isnt it ?
-he is Marakutuka -yeah yeah sorry
now the thing is,
Kusuma gave the plan
Pinto gave Devils Breath powder
blind people did robbery
Moady Nanjappa gave the robbed mall to head constable Annappa
why are you dying to say Annappa it is Marakutuka
you are in illusion !
illusion ? ah ?
Kusuma and Annappa doesnt have any relation
still Kusuma comes to our house
calls you father-in law heartfully
Father in law ?
my father himself sprinkled Devils Breath upon me,
makes me loose my sense
if he had seen then we would have finished ! carefull
-why you brought here ? - i will go
why you always will be in illusion ?
go and see your work
that was my illusion !
yes...correct illusion !
Mr.Annappa, According to law you are under arrest..
appreciated man ! kudos
you have become Detective from Defective
i didnt came here to hear applause from you
tell me the truth i say
who is behind you in this work ?
till now Lalli(Lalitha) was there now she went
dont crack jokes dad
i will throw you into canal if you make comedy now
say correctly
no body is there im only the Kingpin
for every child, his dad will be hero
why did you become villain dad ?
i thought your Sathya Harishchandra(symbol of truth)
why did you do this kind of work ?
to save those truth and justice what Sathya Harishchandra believed
means ?
there was an institution named "Ashakirana"
for blind childrens in Iduvani
even our Kusuma's sister was studying in that institution
if you eat all of this, then i will buy you new clothes
-ok ah ? -sis !
i will stich you new clothes
in that institution they used to teach them
to stich bell bottom pants and used to do marketing
since blind childrens were stiching the pants,
along with that because of that new design
that Brand becaome popular very soon
everyone come
these are attractive clothes of wonderful designs
prepared by blind children of "Ashakirana" institution
these are the bell bottom pants with low affordable prices and with best quality
just when their life was coming to correct track,
Chamanlal Shet's interest raised upon the land
in which "Ashakiran" institution was there
sir that land is very nearer to city
if we build a cinema talkies there,
we can earn as much as we want
that Shet with the help of inspectors,
planned to grab that land
i have plan for that
see children
donars have come forward to break this old building
and to build a new one
so we shall evacuate this place for some days
we have to stay in some other place
by telling lie, they made all those children shelterless
left them in a strange place at night
after that
they created a fake record that there were no children at that place
to grab that land was their plan
no sir,
can leave children here and go ?
forest sir also dark night
they are children sir
there is no child of adult age otherwise we could grabbed them
climb up man
by loosing the institution which was support for their life
they lost their mates and also thrown into streets
for personal reasons and money
for making damage to many people's lives
upon those inspectors,
to take revenge
we did this job by uniting
they after tommorow is the auction of that building
we will buy that building with the robbed money
again we will start 'Ashakirana' institution in the same place
means
did you sell the stolen mall ?
not yet
tommorow party will come to deal with that
then where is the mall ?
these people after burrying that mall under bell bottom tree
i used to go there sir
me after digging
after dumping unter bell bottom tree,
for identification i used to grow mango plant above that
all the stolen malls till now
is under that bell bottom tree
that place is more familiar to you
our regular love spot
-open the door.. what are you doing ?
-open the door
im not arresting you,
for the only reason that your intention was good
but i will wont give mall for any reason
open the door
dont spoil their life,
remove the door
Gurupada keep an eye on them,
i will come now
dont play in this matter
handover our mall back to us
why should i lie dad ?
there was no mall when i reached there
it was there these much days how comes suddenly it misses ?
you have hidden it and now acting in front of us
so what ?
after submitting to court,
do you want to place a big throne on your head ?
please believe me
someone has escaped with mall,
even before i reach there
all those who have info about it are here only
how can third man steal that thing ?
in your gang
other than you people, isnt nobody there ?
no one is there Boss
even im operating secretly
how can information leak ?
why are you looking at me ?
i will be always with you right ?
yes
where is that Quereshi ?
there was a guy called Quereshi here
where did he went ?
yesterday itself he went to his town along with his family
by believing that Diwakara we are spoiled Sahadeva
tomorrow if i wont submit mall to court, i will lose my job
we should count stairs in jail
for that you shoudnt have to wait until tomorrow Mr.Manjunath !
we got the information that you yourselves have stolen station
we even got evidence
why should we rob our own station sir ?
then where is the recovered mall mister ?
they have stolen station sir
why havent you informed department then ?
that is..
your friend Sahadeva is also coming to jail to give you company
what did i do sir ?
for doing shoot out in public place for your personal reasons
we have even arrested Parashuram
we are taking even you for custody
we werent able to eat which had came to our hand
if this land belongs to Shet,
our all dreams will be shattered
dad
who knows that we dont have money
you participate in auction,
then we shall arrange money
its the matter of lakhs
dont make comedy
when we do a good job, god will show us a way
you go and do auction on your style go dad
go
survey number 76/3
11 acres and 16 scense
auction of government land starts now
government challenge !
5 lakhs !
6 lakhs
-six lakh first ca.. -six and half lakhs
six and half lakhs !
8 lakhs first call
-8 lakhs second cal.. -10 lakhs !
10 lakhs first call
ten and half lakh
10 and half lakhs first call
eleven and half
eleven and half first call
-11 and half second call -fifteen lakhs  !
fifteen lakhs
15 lakhs first call
15 lakhs second call
-15 lakhs thir... -fifteen and half lakhs
-go -15 and half lakhs first call
-15 and half se.. -twenty lakhs !
twenty lakhs
20 lakhs first call
20 lakhs second call
20 lakhs final call !
even if you give me free, i wont take this house of owl
my auction, cancel it
-go -is that ok sir ?
you are the next bidder after him
come
annappa.. come gowdre
-sit
fifty percent means it will be 7,75,000
you have cash right ?
if you dont pay cash then land will be went to next bidder
i have talked with party
sell the mall and come with money
why fifty percent ? i will settle entire money
Lally.. you came at right time
means..
these are all your arrangement ah ?
you made us to doubt that innocent Quereshi and,
you escaped mall with your window ?
shut your mouth
you gave us unnessesary tension boss
you should have informed us about this
see Pinto
if we share our secret with air,
then even plants and trees will get to know
then there is no use of complaining air
father in law you didnt said to me also
let it be
whatever may be you didnt believe your own son
does it matter if plate is made of gold or mud ?
what matters is what we eat
money came at right time na ?
Detective Detective
-sign it
-give sir
-Annappa will do something
-why so urgent ?
keep quiet
'Ashakirana' institution for welfare of blind children
let bride come
Pinto move aside
hey Annappa here also urgent ah ?
dont go pushing
-move aside -you move
-you go man -go aside
-dont want -dont want
finally you made house window into house main door right ?
hey your mother
where is the milk ?
remove it and see
ours is fantastic couple
i have a doubt
when this blind people spread agarbatthi powder inside station
everyone will be uncounscious
but it hasnt effected them why ?
that is
to their Agarbhathhi powder and
to this Rathnavarni leaves had farest relation
thats why
30 minutes prior to their station going schedule,
i used to feed dish of Rathnavarni leaves to them
thats the reason they are unaffected
antidose
for what else you have kept antidose ?
you will get to know as time goes, Switch off the light..
Subtitle Edited by Twitter.com/TamilRasanai